<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>-- MARKET -- Real Estate Video Blog with -- CLIENT NAME --</title>
    <description>Our mission at Title &amp; Escrow Guide is to be your best resource for  real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Title &amp; Escrow Guide, your professional  Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 11:05:18 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 11:05:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let Me Be Your Title and Escrow Guide</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/SmCm4fvt0n4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’ve got questions about the real estate process, we’ve got the answers you need.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real estate is changing rapidly these days. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But even with all of these changes taking place, title and escrow have stayed so consistent that even professionals within the industry are beginning to tire of the monotony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We want to help buyers and sellers to better understand real estate.%20http://localhost:4000/let-me-be-your-title-and-escrow-guide.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We want to help buyers and sellers to better understand real estate.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s exactly why I’m here today. &lt;strong&gt;I’m Derek Lockett, your Title and Escrow guide, and I’m ready to shake things up.&lt;/strong&gt; I plan to bring you relevant, helpful, and easy-to-understand content that cuts straight to the point. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our goal is twofold. We want to help buyers and sellers to better understand real estate and we want to help real estate professionals modernize their service. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team and I are excited to start delivering these bite-sized messages to you. If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 09:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/let-me-be-your-title-and-escrow-guide.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/let-me-be-your-title-and-escrow-guide.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
